LUN JI

☑ linus.ji.001@gmail.com https://pegasusor001.github.io/ 6047290794 P North York, Toronto, ON

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/lun-ji-121165155/ Ohttps://github.com/Pegasusor001

SUMMARY

Junior full-stack developer with a strong background in Biochemistry and mathematics. My passion for learning how things work and solving complex problems makes me interested in solving business needs with clean and efficient code. Additionally, my experience with ecommerce product development allowed me to strengthen my skillset in web development and design.

EDUCATION

May 2021 - Aug. 2021 LIGHTHOUSE LAB

Diploma Full-stack web development 2021

Sept. 2016 - Sept. 2019 UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA

Master of Science Biochemistry 2016 GPA: 3.85

UNIVERSITY OF BRITISH COLUMBIA

Sept. 2012 - May 2016

Master of Science Forestry 2019 GPA: 3.95, Graduating With Honors

EMPLOYMENT

Procter & Gamble, *Technology Manager*, BeiJing

Dec. 2019 - Mar. 2021

- Collect, analyze and visualize data from production to selling using Python, JMP, Golden Pocket and Tableau. Provided solutions to ecommerce product design, supply chain and manufacturing optimization.
- Design and deliver end to end package solution for Asian Dry Laundry Fabric Care Business.
- Manage fast, complex detergent initiatives from concept, product and process design through the supply chain startup.
- · Created cost-saving initiative by developing and commercializing recyclable package material.

Advanced Renewable Material Lab, Graduate Researcher, Vancouver

Sept. 2016 - Sept. 2019

- Developed a new technique that significantly improved the accuracy of characterization of polymers.
- · Achieved publication in Green Chemistry for an entry entitled "Greener Isolation of Phenolic Monomers from Kraft Lignin using Magnetically Recyclable TEMPO Nanocatalyst", 2019,21, 785-791.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JAVASCRIPT, HTML, SQL, CSS, PYTHON, VBA, C++, MATLAB:

FRAMEWORKS/ LIBRARIES / ENVIRONMENTS: NODEJS, REACTJS, EXPRESS, RAILS, SOCKETSJO, WEBSOCKETS, JQUERY,

DATABASE: POSTGRESQL, ACCESS:

PROJECTS

July 2021 - Aug. 2021 **Budget Manager**

An application that helps clients to manage their budget and visualize their spending. It also allows clients to speak with the expert on real time.

Frameworks: Express, Node, React, WebSockets, PostgreSQL, ThreeJS, SASS.

June 2021 - July 2021 Amazon-Clone

a clone version of amazon. A user can view product list and order items.

Frameworks: Express, Node, Ruby on Rails, EJS, PostgreSQL

Food Delivery May 2021 - June 2021

A restaurant website that allows user to explore cuisines and order items. Frameworks: Express, jQuery, Node, SASS, PostgreSQL, Twilio API